# BEATRICE OANA STANILA

**IUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** 







07376552619

Coventry, West Midlands

## **Profile Summary**

Ambitious, resilient, team player with a passion for personal growth and problem-solving. Experience working in healthcare and hospitality. I am currently on the lookout for software development opportunities, having successfully completed the Full Stack JavaScript Development Bootcamp at the School of Code.

## Stack

- JavaScript
- React.js
- Next.js
- TailwindCSS
- CSS & HTML
- Express.js

PostgreSQL

- Firebase Auth NoSQL Database (MongoDB)
- REST/ restful API

## Testing

- Postman
- lest
- Cypress
- React Testing Library
- VS Code Debugging

## **Working Methodology**

- · Agile Scrum ceremonies
- Pair Programming
- Branching GitHub
- Trello, Figma, Miro
- Weekly Hackathons
- CI/CD pipeline

## **Education**

## **Full Stack JavaScript Web Developer**

School of Code, Remote - UK

### **Pharmacy Bachelor's Degree**

Victor Babes - Univeristy of Medicine and Pharmacy, Timisoara, RO

#### 09/2022 - 01/2023

09/2014 - 09/2019

## **Projects**

#### AMIGO - A Travel Platform for Exploring Lesser-Demo ⊗ | GitHub Repo ⊗ **Known Destinations.**

- This project was built during the last month of the School of Code bootcamp, in a team of 6 people.
- My contribution was by working on multiple aspects of the development process including the ideation, the database, the frontend, authentication features, testing, deploying, and styling.

JavaScript | Next | PostgreSQL | Node | Express | Netlify Firebase Auth | Axios | TailwindCSS | OpenTripMap API

#### FLASH - The Ultimate App for Bootcamp Graduates' Interview Preparation. Demo ⊗ | GitHub Repo ⊗

- During week 9 of the bootcamp, our team of four collaborated to design an app that aids bootcampers and other individuals in preparing for job interviews.
- Throughout the project, I focused primarily on frontend development, utilizing React to enhance my proficiency with the library.

JavaScript | React | PostgreSQL | Node | Express | Render Axios | Jest & Supertest | Postman | CSS Modules

### **Work Experience**

## Pharmacovigilance Specialist, ProPharma Group - Remote, UK

02/2022 - 09/2022

- Wrote comprehensive Nuvaxovid vaccine narrative reports and presented them to stakeholders.
- Meticulously carried out daily case processing for reported adverse events, including information gathering during follow-up calls, as well as written communications to obtain further details.

### Pharmacy Assistant, Boots - Coventry, UK

03/2020-01/2022

- As the Patient Safety Champion, I worked closely with the team to ensure that each patient received the best possible care and that any potential risks were identified and addressed on time.
- · Provided individualized advice that enabled customers to make well-informed decisions about their healthcare needs.

### Interests

- Future Technologies: Redux, TypeScript, Python, AWS, Codewars.
- Travelling participated in the USA Work & Travel programme.
- Fitness (gym, social dancing, hiking, ice-skating) | Formula 1 | Literature | Languages.